Prayer for anxiety.
Great is Yahweh, worthy of all praise—merciful and gracious, slow to anger, rich
in love and truth.
The heavens declare Your glory; You made the heavens and the earth. I adore You,
Elohim.
Faithful God, I confess my sins—intentional and unintentional. I’ve forgotten
Your grace.
Search me, know my heart, and renew a steadfast spirit in me.
With thanksgiving I enter Your courts. Thank You for life and daily bread, and
for salvation in Christ, who loved us and died for us.
Even in trials, teach me to count it joy and grow endurance.
Sovereign Lord, nothing is hidden from You.
Jesus, You invite the weary to find rest.
I bring my anxiety and this condition—(state it)—under Your gentle yoke.
Guard my mind, guide my steps, and make Your Word my steady rhythm.
Open support for all who are under heavy pressure.
I commit my plans to You. I release control—Your will be done.
In Jesus’ name, Amen.