Prayer for success
All the earth will worship You and sing to Your name.
God, Your way is perfect; Your Word is proven.
The sea is Yours; Your hands formed the dry land.
Yahweh Sabaoth—Lord of Armies—You reign.
Lord of mercy, to You belongs forgiveness.
I confess my intentional and unintentional sins; I’ve strayed in word and deed.
Let me forsake my way and return to You—abundantly pardon me.
Restore to me the joy of Your salvation and uphold me with a willing spirit.
Yours, Yahweh, is the greatness, the power, the glory, the victory, and the
majesty!
Thank You for life, for daily bread, and for salvation— no condemnation for
those in Christ Jesus.
In weakness, let Your grace be sufficient and Your power made perfect.
Sovereign Lord, teach me to seek first Your Kingdom and righteousness.
I bring my condition before You: help me live in my work and calling.
Grant diligence, wisdom, and favor to all seeking success honorably.
Train me to measure success by faithfulness to You, not worldly gain.
Father, I commit my plans to You.
Not my will, but Yours be done.
In Jesus’ name, Amen.